<indicatorCards>
	<card
		id="1"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Multi-lingual Disaster Communication"
		definition="The extent to which all people can easily access information about disaster preparedness, post-disaster and emergency response."
		resilienceValue="Communication, education, and information sharing by local agencies are critical to efforts to avoid, respond to, and recover from disaster events and climate hazards."
		equityValue="Communication should be conducted in multiple languages and formats to ensure it is easily accesssible and culturally appropriate to the entire community."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Community Text alert registration and list serves"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="If the community is using a technological solution such as a text alert system, how many people and what percentage of the population is registered for that alert system? Does it provide inforamtion in multiple languages that are appropriate for the community."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Contact your local emergency management operations professionals and identify relevant emergency and evacuation notification protocols specific to your community. 2. Review what technologies, tools, and methods are being utilized. 3. Have conversations with community members across a wide variety of demographics and socioeconomic scales to identify whether or not all of the community understands how to effectively access this information. 4. Coordinate with the local emergency operations team to identify gaps and solutions to accessibility issues for disaster preparedness measures. (add meeting with leaders - number leaders)"
		additionalInformation="Communication, education, and information sharing are critical to efforts to avoid, respond to, and recover from disaster events and climate hazards. Consider that federal databases on language proficiency are generally not accurate for this indicator, because it is often used as a proxy for immigration status and may be underreported. As a result, local immigrant support organizations may be your best access for this issue. This issue matters most when you want to inform, educate, collaborate, or otherwise communicate with people who may not speak your language. The best outcomes occur when you can ensure you are reaching your whole community, using the language that best utilizes their full capacity to interact and contribute meaningfully."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How accessible are emergency and disaster preparedness, response, and recovery resources, support, and messaging to all community members?"/>
			<question text="Are warning messages (e.g. reverse 911, text alerts, community sirens) and technologies culturally relevant and understandable by community members?"/>
			<question text="Are messages and platforms available and accessible in all relevant languages?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="2"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Financial Security"
		definition="The share of people whose individual or household income is at least 200% the Federal Poverty Threshold."
		resilienceValue="Financial security and economic opportunity is important for community health and well-being and the ability to prepare for and recover from disasters."
		equityValue="Financial security within a community can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Headwaters Economics Economic Profile System - Demographics Report Tool and/or Populations at Risk Tool; ATSDR/CDC SVI; US Census ACS"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Headwaters Economics Economic Profile System: headwaterseconomics.org/apps/economic-profile-system/ 2. Enter your area of interest (city, county, etc.) in the search bar. 3. Download the &quot;Populations at Risk&quot; Report by clicking on the blue download icon. 4. Open the Populations at Risk Report and scroll to &quot;Individuals in Poverty&quot; and/or &quot;Families in Poverty&quot;"
		qualitativeDataCollProcess=""
		additionalInformation="Financial security and economic opportunity are powerful predictors of good health. Targeting resilience building efforts to address poverty and increase financial security can improve and support social, economic, environmental, and racial justice and equity.  
High Cost of Living (HCOL) areas effectively raise the economic price line below which you can't really achieve a decent standard of living, and are forced to compromise critical factors that could improve your resilience."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many people living in your community (or what percentage) have incomes above 200% of the Federal Poverty Limit?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers or percentages vary by neighborhood (census tract), race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="3"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Forward-Looking Planning and Operation"
		definition="The extent to which information on current and future conditions (e.g. climate conditions, demographics) is incorporated into local planning documents, conversations, and emergency preparedness operations."
		resilienceValue="Understanding how climate change and other information about the future is incorporated into local plans, evacuation protocols, emergency preparedness operations planning, and health care services can indicate how proactively the community is preparing for these changes."
		equityValue="Local plans should include consideration of the equity impacts of climate change and impacts on different demographic groups and neighborhoods."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Review of local planning documents"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Compile and collect all relevant climate change planning documents that are publicly available (e.g., Climate Adaptation Plan). 2. Work with the core team to review all community plans and count the number of plans that have explictily included future conditions. 3. Have the core team decide on how best to rank the plans and level of future planning included across plans."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Identify contact information for your local planning department (municipal level, county level, state level). 2. Compile and collect all relevant climate change planning documents that are publicly available (e.g., Climate Adaptation Plan). Coordinate with your local planning office or additional departments for additional support. 3. Review all community plans. Identify gaps in climate-informed data and planning at the local and regional levels and determine what efforts are ongoing. 4. Identify opportunities to connect local community-based organizations to ongoing and needed planning efforts focused on climate change."
		additionalInformation="Making the direct connection between these principles and climate changes is a critical first step to prioritizing projects, programs, and policies that support, empower, and protect all community members from climate hazards now and into the future. Metrics can be ranked based on local knowledge from the community. Consider developing a worksheet or guidance that can be used to support the community ranking of the level of inclusion in climate planning. Leave space for (or recommend) that communities identify their own metrics and data sources. Help ensure that the community voices and expertise are included in the assessment of the metric."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How well does your community incorporate climate change and other future projections  into its planning efforts?"/>
			<question text="Does your municipality/county/state have a climate adaptation plan, hazard mitigation plan, community wildfire protection plan, or pre-disaster recovery plan that incorporate future conditions?"/>
			<question text="Does your community's emergency response plan include future projections?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="4"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Equity in Planning and Operation"
		definition="The extent to which equity, justice, inclusion, diversity, and belonging are explicitly included in local planning efforts."
		resilienceValue="Embedding principles of justice, equity, diversity, inclusion, and belonging into planning documents and operations reflect priorities and can support projects, programs, and policies that support, empower, and protect all community members."
		equityValue="Planning should include representation from demographic groups and neighborhoods, particularly those typically excluded."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Review of local planning documents"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Compile and collect all relevant climate change planning documents that are publicly available (e.g., Climate Adaptation Plan). 2. Work with the core team to review all community plans and count the number of plans that have explictily included equity. Consider who was involved in writing the plan, the design of plan, and the operations of the plan. 3. Have the core team decide on how best to rank the plans and level of equity included across plans."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members and community based organizations to determine what [climate] justice, equity, diversity, inclusion, and belonging issues and concerns exist. 2. Identify local and regional planning documents and determine who was involved in the creation of the plans and whether or not they explicitly address climate and environmental justice as priority topic areas. 3. Identify community based organizations that specialize in these topics to support the process. 4. Identify areas of opportunity to embed climate and environmental justice concerns and priorities in all local/regional planning efforts and operations."
		additionalInformation="Embedding equity consideration into the planning process can lead to significant changes in the built environment as well as other system. However, there are other factors to consider. Equity in the built environment may also need to include unionization, adherence to safety measures; building codes that demand housing built to ADA standards; making streets safe and accessible for people with disabilities, older adults, and people with dementia. The AARP has really interesting guidance and data"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How well are the principles of equity, justice, inclusion, diversity, and belonging embedded into climate change planning efforts and operations?"/>
			<question text="Does your municipality/county/state plans (e.g., emergency preparedness plans, land use plans, hazard mitigation plans, etc.) explicitly discuss equity, justice, diversity, inclusion, and belonging?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="5"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Community solidarity"
		definition="The strength of relationships and solidarity among and between members of a community."
		resilienceValue="The strength of relationships between and among groups of residents are important for community health and well-being and the ability to recover from disasters."
		equityValue="Community solidarity may vary within or between neighborhoods or demographic groups."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Community conversations with core team, community organizations, and social connectors. Surveys that ask people to name five neighbors or one elder in their neighborhood, number of community events or neighborhood events they participate in…etc."
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="Work with the Core Team and local community members to identify and count the number of important community gathering spaces and organizations such as churches, neighborhood groups, neighborhood festivals, participation in the neighborhood night out, block parties, community centers, libraries, community events. Sporting events, clubs, and programs can also contribute and could be identified. Consider utilizing a social network analysis method to identify and track connections within and between groups or the IPCR - index of perceived community resilience."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Work with Core Team to consider social cohesion and identify and describe &quot;levels&quot; of cohesion. 2. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high social cohesion. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state). 3. Consult with community based organizations, civic groups, and others to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 4. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="This can be an extremely difficult area to assess, but also one of the most important for community health, wellbeing, and resilience.  There are no good &quot;national&quot; datasets and what is important to a community must be defined by that community.  Consider the existence of different types of social capital (e.g. &quot;bonding capital&quot; that brings a group together and &quot;bridging capital&quot; that brings different groups together).  Both forms are important and it is important to consider social cohesion both within and between groups.  Need to consider if Sense of Place is incorporated here or included separately. Social cohesion can therefore both directly benefit people and indirectly buffer them from risk factors that might otherwise damage their wellbeing and decrease their resilience to hazards, disasters, and threats. The protective nature of social support may be especially important for populations that experience discrimination or exclusion. For example, during natural disasters like heat waves, elderly individuals living in neighborhoods with low social cohesion may lack social support from concerned neighbors who will check on them, and they have fewer safe communal areas where they can seek refuge. See U.S. DHHS Office of Disease Prevention and Health Promotion for more information: https://health.gov/healthy people/priority-areas/social-determinants-health/literature-summaries/social-cohesion"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How vibrant are the social network in your community both within and between groups?"/>
			<question text="Do community members actively participate in and utilize neighborhood facilities, organizations, and gathering spaces?"/>
			<question text="Are the networks stronger/weaker in some groups or some parts of the community?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="6"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Physical and Mental Health"
		definition="The extent to which community members are physically and mentally healthy."
		resilienceValue="Physical and mental health are important for community well-being and the ability to withstand and recover from disasters."
		equityValue="Physical and mental health within a community can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="CDC PLACES provides nation-wide census tract level estimates for a wide variety of major diseases, e.g. diabetes, kidney disease, cancer, heart disease, high blood pressure, etc. USALEEP provides life expectancy values for all U.S. States. 
Local Public Health agencies can provide more detailed disease incidence summaries in many jurisdictions."
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Examine the CDC PLACES mapper to determine which health conditions are important in your community. Based on this survey, determine which factors you need to highlight. 2. Utilize the &quot;GIS Friendly&quot; CDC PLACES datasets to determine tract-level patterns of disease incidence. 3. Utilize whatever local, county, or state public health datasets are available that are relevant to both physical and mental health. Confer with Public Health personnel if possible to determine local issues and known areas of concern."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high physical and mental health throughout the community and in specific neighborhoods. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state). 2. Consult with community based organizations, civic groups, and others to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="There are a significant number of health concerns that are mapped by the CDC PLACES index. Communities can select the diseases that are most prevalent and/or have the most connection with the hazards, disasters, and threats identified by the community. It is also appropriate to consider how to best complement these national data summaries with locally relevant and specific data from community, county, or state health departments. Consider if it is useful for a community to pull out individual disease burdens with known climate connections (asthma, COPD, Diabetes, etc.) individually in the indicator menu or leave this category general and allow the community to customize the metrics as needed. Health concerns within a community can vary dramatically across racial, economic, and ethnic lines, and must be considered in the cultural and historical contexts that shape them, especially in areas of high air pollution, toxic site exposure, lead exposure, mining waste exposure, and other components of the local built environment that may induce increased incidence and severity of physical health conditions. Resilient delivery of services during normal conditions as well as during emergency scenarios must be able to address the array of local needs that characterize local communities and neighborhoods. What specific considerations do populations have for emergency response and evacuation? Does the community track households requiring electricity for medical equipment, those with limited mobility, or other support services?"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="What is the general health and mental and physical well-being of the community?"/>
			<question text="What diseases are present and how do they negatively affect community members health? How many people and what percentage of the population are affected by each of these diseases?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
		<card
		id="7"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Health Care Access"
		definition="The extent to which community members have health insurance and access to care."
		resilienceValue="Acces to health care, including health insurance coverage and availability of providers, is critical for supporting the physical and mental health of community members."
		equityValue="The share of individuals with health insurance coverage can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="PLACES: Local Data for Better Health, 2021 Release. Accessed at: https://www.cdc.gov/places/"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Neighborhoods at Risk at https://bit.ly/3P8x4Ec 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “households without health insurance” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable. 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high access to health insurance and health care coverage.  Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state). 2. Consult with community based organizations, civic groups, and others to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="Adequate and accessible care can treat disease factors early and decrease sensitivity to climate-driven hazards or help individuals and families recover more quickly with lower financial burdens after an event. Be conscious that some people with insurance may be under-insured and/or unable to easily and affordably access care. Insurance coverage does not necessarily equate to access to care. Frequently rural community members and ethnic and racial minorities have fewer choices and less access to care or are less likely to access that care even if it is available."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many people/families (or what percentages) have an adequate level of health insurance?"/>
			<question text="How many clinics, primary care facilities, and providers are there per capita?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers or percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="8"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Full employment"
		definition="The share of people over the age of 18 that are fully  employed."
		resilienceValue="Employed members of the community have more economic stability and are generally better able to invest in preparedness or respond to unexpected shocks and stressors."
		equityValue="The share of people fully employed can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="U.S. Census Bureau. (2019). 2014-2018 American Community Survey 5-year Public Use Microdata Samples, Block Groups &#38; Larger Areas [CSV Data file]. https://www.nhgis.org/  - S2303"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Headwaters Economics Economic Profile System: headwaterseconomics.org/apps/economic-profile-system/ 2. Enter your area of interest (city, county, etc.) in the search bar. 3. Download the &quot;Socioeconomic Trends&quot; Report by clicking on the blue download icon. 4. Open the Socioeconomic Trends Report and scroll to &quot;Unemployment&quot; For Tract-Level Data: 1. Go to the CDC/ATSDR Social Vulnerability Index Mapping Tool or download the appropriate GIS dataset: atsdr.cdc.gov/placeandhealth/svi/ 2. Download the appropriate GIS dataset or Locate your community and the census tracts of interest using the interactive mapping tool. 3. Record the appropriate data points."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess=""
		additionalInformation="Employment status and employment rates may be an indicator of the overall health and vitality of the economic system. May need to separate out &quot;unemployed&quot; with the &quot;underemployed, temporary, or gig workers&quot;. Unemployed workers will have lower economic stability and thus greater vulnerability to shocks and stresses. Gig workers have a less reliable source of income and less access to benefits such as health insurance, making them more susceptible to shocks."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many people (of working age)  are employed / unemployed?"/>
			<question text="What share are underemployed, temporary, or gig workers?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="9"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Access to Healthy Food"
		definition="The extent to which access to  nutritional food is available."
		resilienceValue="The availability of healthy food is an important contributor to community health and well-being."
		equityValue="Access to healthy food can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Headwaters Economics Economic Profile System - Populations at Risk Tool; US Census ACS; USDA Food Atlas"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Headwaters Economics Economic Profile System: headwaterseconomics.org/apps/economic-profile-system/ 2. Enter your area of interest (city, county, etc.) in the search bar. 3. Download the &quot;Populations at Risk&quot; Report by clicking on the blue download icon. 4. Open the Populations at Risk Report and scroll to &quot;Households Receiving Public Assistance&quot;"
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high access healthy food options.  Make sure to work with the core team to identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state) and provide guidance on the low, medium, and high levels. 2. Consult with community based organizations, civic groups, and others to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="While SNAP participation can provide some information to support this indicator, Local food access advocacy organizations (e.g., Food Banks) can provide critical additional information about food accessibility and challenges in your community. If possible, consult with local food access experts to understand the specific challenges vulnerable and historically marginalized populations may face regarding food, food security, food access, and food quality. SNAP benefits recipients are only one part of the complex food security puzzle. Healthy people are generally more able to respond to extreme events and disasters and will require less assistance during those events."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many people live within 0.5 miles of healthy food stores?"/>
			<question text="What percentage of the population is considered food secure or are receiving
receiving SNAP benefits?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="10"
		system="Social Environment"
		indicator="Access to personal or public transportation"
		definition="The extent to which residents have sufficient access to a motorized vehicle and/or public transportation."
		resilienceValue="Access to public transportation or a private vehicle is critical for economic opportunity and access to education, food, health, and other services as well as evacuation during extreme weather events."
		equityValue="Access to transportation can vary dramatically across racial/ethnic, age, gender, nationality, and economic lines."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Neighborhoods at Risk; U.S. Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year Estimates"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Neighborhoods at Risk at https://bit.ly/3P8x4Ec 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “households with no car” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable. 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high access and use of active transportation.  Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state).      2. Consult with community based organizations, civic groups, and others to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience. 4.Conduct a qualitative ranking of transit accessibility, ranging from Poor (no stops within ½ mile) to Excellent (multiple stops within ¼ mile)"
		additionalInformation="Places with a high percentage of people using active modes of transportation tend to be more walkable and more accessible to destinations where jobs, schools, groceries and other necessities are available. The transit network and the use of the transit networks actually an interconnection between social and build environments. Car ownership has historically be a proxy for financial stability and independence, but that is changing. Vehicles can be extremely important in getting out of harms way from many environmental threats, especially if public infrastructure is damaged or there are power outages."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many people (what percentage) use active transportation options on a regular basis?"/>
			<question text="What percentage of the population has access to a vehicle?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="11"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Access to Cooling Spaces"
		definition="Resident access to cool space including parks, shade, cooling centers, and areas with low urban heat island temperatures."
		resilienceValue="Access to cooling spaces, particularly during extreme heat events, can limit impacts on young people, older adults, and individuals with physical conditions that decrease their ability to thermally regulate their body temperature."
		equityValue="There is a disporportionate distribution of impervious surfaces (concrete, asphalt, gravel, roofs) that concentrate heat and raise local temperatures in Black and poor communities and neighborhoods."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Trust for Public Lands map"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess=""
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high heat island exposure. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state). 2. Consult with local planners, public works, and/or research (or equivalent) personnel to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="Extreme heat is the leading cause of weather-related mortality in the United States, killing more people than any other type of weather-related event. In some regions, the number of extreme heat days are nearly certain to increase along with high average humidity levels. Previous research has identified that the distribution of impervious surfaces (concrete, asphalt, gravel, roofs) that concentrate heat and raise local temperatures present a disproportionate burden upon the city’s Black and poor communities. Trust for Public Lands has a nationwide dataset (updatied on a rolling basis). See: https://www.arcgis.com/home/item.html?id=4f6d72903c9741a6a6ee6349f5393572"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="Are there specific characteristics of particular neighborhoods that lead to decreased or increased heat island effect exposure (e.g., more/less tree canopy coverage)?"/>
			<question text="Are cooling centers equipped to provide safe space for elderly, LGTBQIA+, youth, and other communities?"/>
			<question text="Where can community members access cooling centers?"/>
			<question text="How do they decide to access those centers?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="12"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Households with internet subscriptions"
		definition="Housing units with internet access AND a subscription to that service."
		resilienceValue="Internet access enables community members to access critical emergency preparedness and disaster responses information."
		equityValue="Internet access increasingly provides critical daily information and access to other community services, such as medical services. It also helps keep people socially connected. However, internet service is very costly in the United States, the most expensive globally, and many lower income households cannot afford regular service. Rural areas especially struggle to provide stable and afforadable internet access."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="ACS Dataset: Table B28002 &quot;PRESENCE AND TYPES OF INTERNET SUBSCRIPTIONS IN HOUSEHOLD&quot; or Table B28003 &quot;PRESENCE OF A COMPUTER AND TYPE OF INTERNET SUBSCRIPTION IN HOUSEHOLD&quot;"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access the US Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year Estimates at https://data.census.gov/ 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “Internet Subscriptions (S2801)” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="Host discussion with community members and community organizations.  Consult with local planners, public works, and/or research (or equivalent) personnel to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area."
		additionalInformation=""
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many (what percentage of) households have access to the internet via a local subscription?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="13"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Distance to Hazardous Sites"
		definition="The number and condition of manmade hazardous sites (brownfields, hazardous substance locations, toxic industrial activity, hazardous waste treatment facilities) within or in close proximity to the community."
		resilienceValue="A safe and healthy community is supported by a healthy environment and not at risk of contamination from toxic materials stored at hazardous sites. Communities at sufficient distance and not downstream of hazardous or toxic sites are less likely to be severely affected by pollution during extreme weather events."
		equityValue="The distance to hazardous sites can vary dramatically across racial, economic, and ethnic lines. Communities located closer to hazardous sites bear the disproportionate burden of potential pollution during extreme weather events."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Environmental Protection Agency Environmental Justice Screening Tool"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access the EPA Environmental Justice Screening Tool. 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to &quot;superfund sites&quot; in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable. 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or exposure to hazardous waste treatment and disposal facility sources for households or neighborhoods. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, municipality, county, state). 1. Consult with your regional EPA office (or equivalent) to determine the number of hazardous sites locally/regionally. 2. Consult with local planners, public works, and/or research (or equivalent) personnel to determine specific concerns identified across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="This indicator is important to consider whether or not individual locations and distances can be determined. 
Cross check the hazardous site locations with known and current/future projected climate hazard areas. Are there any concerns with future contamination and spread? Superfund or National Priority List sites are polluted locations, usually as a result of unregulated or illegal industrial activity, that require log-term responses for clean up of hazardous materials. Impacts to natural resources, biodiversity, and human health associated with these sites effectively preclude them from safe habitation or use. Risk Management Plan facilities are facilities whose processes, products, or ingredients present the threat of serious harm should they breach containment or should some other type of accident occur. Risk Management Plan facilities are facilities whose processes, products, or ingredients present the threat of serious harm should they breach containment or should some other type of accident occur. These facilities are frequently located in or near historically underserved and overburdened communities. In cases of extreme weather events, pollutants/contaminants can be dispersed and impact critical water resources through flooding, for example. . In addition to the direct threats caused during an event, indirect outputs from the facilities can affect the health and wellbeing of households in the surrounding areas."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many hazardous sites exist in and around the community?"/>
			<question text="How much of the community lives more than 5 km from superfund, industrial, or hazardous sites and what condition are those sites?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="14"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Housing: Secure Renters"
		definition="Rental Housing Units whose residents spend less than 30%  of their monthly income on rent and household utility bills."
		resilienceValue="Renters are those who spend less than 30% of their income on their rent and utilities are less vulnerable to displacement during economic or natural shocks and stressors."
		equityValue="For low income residents, it is important to consider the quality of housing available at this price point to ensure the physical and mental health of the individuals and families in that space."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="U.S. Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year estimates"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access the US Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year Estimates at https://data.census.gov/ 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “housing units that are occupied by renters” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high levels of shelter secure renters. 2. Cross check that information with community organizations or municipal departments."
		additionalInformation="For low income residents, it is important to consider the quality of housing available at this price point to ensure the physical and mental health of the individuals and families in that space.  For a deeper understanding of these issues, the number and percentage of renters can be correlated with the age and quality of the building stock to look for patterns in use of lower quality homes and residents by renters.   Description modified from the CA Healthy Places Index https://policies.healthyplacesindex.org/housing/severely-cost-burdened-low-income-homeowners/about"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many (what percentage) of the renters are spending less than 30% of their income on their rent and utilities?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="15"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Housing: Secure Homeowners"
		definition="Housing Units Occupied by Homeowners who own their homes and whose monthly costs for mortgage and utilities are less than 30% of household income."
		resilienceValue="Homeowners spend less than 30% of their income on their mortgage and utilities are less vulnerability to displacement during economic or natural shocks and stressors."
		equityValue="For low income residents, it is important to consider the quality of housing available at this price point to ensure the physical and mental health of the individuals and families in that space. Gentrification is a critical concern in the equity landscape, and housing costs are one dimension of economic pressure through which gentrification can displace multigenerational homeowners."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="U.S. Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year estimates"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access the US Census Bureau American Community Survey 5-year Estimates at https://data.census.gov/ 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “housing units that are occupied by renters” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high levels of shelter secure homeowners. 2. Cross check that information with community organizations or municipal departments."
		additionalInformation="For low income residents, it is important to consider the quality of housing available at this price point to ensure the physical and mental health of the individuals and families in that space.  Gentrification is a critical concern in the equity landscape, and housing costs are one dimension of economic pressure through which gentrification can displace multigenerational homeowners. 
For a deeper understanding of these issues, the number and percentage of homeowners can be correlated with the age and quality of the building stock to look for patterns in use of lower quality homes and residents by renters. Description modified from the CA Healthy Places Index https://policies.healthyplacesindex.org/housing/severely-cost-burdened-low-income-homeowners/about"
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many (what percentage) of homeowners are spending less than 30% of their income on their mortgage and utilities?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="16"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Emergency routes"
		definition="Number and quality of emergency routes away from potential hazards."
		resilienceValue="A transportation network with built in redundancy and limited bottle necks is critical for safe and smooth evacuation."
		equityValue="Evacuation routes can vary dramatically across racial, economic, and ethnic lines. Routes need to be equitably distributed across all neighborhoods and appropriately sized for the number of residents in areas of high density."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Maps, land use plans, flood plain maps, evacuation plans, hazard mitigation plans, and GIS analysis of &quot;traffic sheds&quot;"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Work with emergency management staff at the local or county level to identify how they track evacuation routes. 2. Detailed analysis can be performed using local roadway and housing data if the community has GIS analyist capabilities."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Work with public works and emergency management staff to determine the level of access to safe and redundant evacuation routes (low, medium, high). Work with core team to define those levels as relevant to the community. 2. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high levels of access to safe and redundant evacuation routes. 3. Cross check that information with community organizations or municipal departments."
		additionalInformation=""
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="For each neighborhood in the community, are there at least two routes to move out of harm's way? Consider a variety of potential extreme weather events independently and those that may occur at the same time."/>
			<question text="How do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="17"
		system="Built Environment"
		indicator="Emergency Shelters"
		definition="Number of and ability to access appropriate and dedicated shelters used during disasters and/or major events."
		resilienceValue="Emergency Shelters or Community Resilience Centers can be especially important in helping to provide essential services in challenging times."
		equityValue="Access to safe and appropriate emergency shelters can vary dramatically across racial, economic, and ethnic lines. Emergency shelters need to be equitably distributed across all neighborhoods and adequately equipped to appropriately and safely house different community types to provide essential services during disasters and/or major events."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Local emergency management county contact"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Contact your local emergency management county representative. 2. Evaluate the answers and proximity of all neighborhoods to the emergency shelters. 3. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 4. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable 5. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high levels of shelter secure homeowners. 2. Cross check that information with community organizations or municipal departments."
		additionalInformation="These centers need to be accessible by a variety of community members and a variety of weather conditions. Ideally, they are co-designed with the community so that the center provides value to the community both during a disaster and on a daily basis."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How many emergency shelters or resilience centers are there and how are they distributed across the community?"/>
			<question text="Are emergency shelters equipped to safely and appropriately house different community types present in their neighborhood including elderly, LGBTQIA+, youth, etc?"/>
			<question text="What is the average or typical evacuation distance for residents to access a shelter?"/>
			<question text="What is the average or typical ease of access to emergency shelters, especially for those who use public transit, walk, bike or otherwise do not have access to a car?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="18"
		system="Natural Environment"
		indicator="Tree Canopy Coverage"
		definition="The percent of tree canopy coverage by neighborhood across a community."
		resilienceValue="Trees provide a wide variety of benefits for a neighborhood including shade for cooling, absorption of precipitation during heavy rainfall events, and absorption of pollution."
		equityValue="Areas with lower tree canopy coverage are frequently correlated with historical patterns of racist segregation as white, wealthy neighborhoods are much more likely to have high levels of tree canopy coverage."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Neighborhoods at Risk: https://headwaterseconomics.org/tools/neighborhoods-at-risk/tool-about/"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="1. Access Neighborhoods at Risk at https://bit.ly/3P8x4Ec 2. Use the search bar to identify your community. 3. Select the filter applicable to “area lacking tree canopy” in your community. 4. Evaluate the answers to the Data questions. 5. Supplement and/or refine the numbers above with local data, if applicable. 6. Use the data to determine next steps."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high tree canopy coverage. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (is this a particular community, neighborhood, and/or they whole municipality). 2. Consult with local parks and recreation (or equivalent) personnel to determine the spatial extent of tree canopy coverage across the specified area. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="Areas with lower tree canopy coverage are frequently correlated with historical patterns of racist segregation as white, wealthy neighborhoods are much more likely to have high levels of tree canopy coverage. Consider rural areas, municipalities in ecosystems without many trees (desert southwest), etc. Consider three primary tiers of information - the community as a whole, neighborhoods/subsets of the community, areas with known elevated flood or wildfire exposure.  Also consider the health and vitality of the forests or trees in each area, for example, unmaintained street trees may pose hazards to local residents when they drop mature branches or displace sidewalk infrastructure. Also consider how forestry, particularly urban forest management will be affected by changing climate conditions (hotter temperatures, more disease or pests)...etc."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="Do the neighborhoods in the community each have low, medium, or high tree canopy coverage?"/>
			<question text="What percentage of the neighborhood's total land surface area is tree canopy coverage?"/>
			<question text="At a finer level, are the trees in places where they shade walkable streets, transit stops, or public spaces and buildings?"/>
			<question text="Do these numbers or percentages vary by neighborhood (census tract), race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>
	<card
		id="19"
		system="Natural Environment"
		indicator="Parks, Green spaces, and Blue spaces"
		definition="The percentage of all acres within and across a community that were identified as being in a park, recognized greenspace, or blue space, including both private and public parks and waterways."
		resilienceValue="Parks, Greenspaces, and Blue Spaces (rivers, lakes, beaches and land nearby) are critical in supporting human health (mental and social as well as physical exercise etc.), can cool surrounding areas, and absorb extreme rainfall."
		equityValue="Areas with lower access to greenspace are frequently correlated with historical patterns of racist segregation as white, wealthy neighborhoods are much more likely to have high levels of access to greenspace."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="Trust for Public Lands map"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="There are a few roads to this data. The Trust for Public Lands maintains greenspace/park access information for most CONUS metros. NAIP imagery programs also make green surface detection possible (see Cincinnati Climate Equity Indicators Report). Local public works/parks department shapefile data (with or without &quot;private&quot; parks included) may also be available."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Consult with local parks and recreation (or equivalent) personnel to determine the spatial extent of parks and greenspaces known to the relevant community governments. Public Works departments may also have GIS data useful for determining exact position of parks and other greenspaces in your area. 2. Utilize tools, such as the Trust for Public Lands Parkserve (parkserve.tpl.org) to identify other greenspaces in your area of interest. 3. Identify if there are significant portions of the community without convenient access to known greenspaces."
		additionalInformation="It is important to consider the quality of these greenspaces and not just the existence of the greenspace, for example overgrown or weedy vegetation from lack of maintenance can be a burden to local communities rather than a benefit. To expand the use of the space and the utility to the community, presence of publicly accessible bathrooms, number of park benches, amount of shade, ADA accessible portions of the area are all important for older adults and people with disabilities."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="What percentage of the community is park, greenspace, or blue space?"/>
			<question text="How many households live within 0.5 miles  of a park, greenspace, or blue space?"/>
			<question text="How do these numbers and percentages vary by neighborhood, race, or ethnicity?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="20"
		system="Natural Environment"
		indicator="Critical Ecosystem Health"
		definition="The health and wellbeing of ecosystems in and surrounding the community."
		resilienceValue="Ecosystems provide a variety of physical, social, cultural, and economic values and support the well-being of communities."
		equityValue="The health of critical ecosystems can vary dramatically across neighborhoods and racial, economic, and ethnic lines, based on access to resources and environmental protective measures."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="https://www.epa.gov/report-environment/diversity-and-biological-balance#roe-indicators"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="This process depends on the place and the ecosystem, and so could be done many different ways. One way to get started is to browse the EPA ROE national indicators (https://www.epa.gov/report-environment/diversity-and-biological-balance#roe-indicators ) for locally relevant data. Next, search for local and state data sources on these topics."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high ecosystem health for one or more ecosystems. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (one particular ecosystem, several, etc.). 2. Consult with local parks and recreation, ecologists, and research personnel to determine past, current, and future characteristics of ecosystem health and how that may have changed (and will continue to) due to climate change. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="Although most U.S. citizens live in developed and exurban environments, access to natural ecosystems and the function of natural ecosystems play a critical role in the well-being of all human populations.  Access to natural landscapes and their varied benefits are also a central concern of discussions on equity that recognize historical economic and racial discrimination that affect access to and familiarity with natural ecosystems. Consider past and future conditions - is the ecosystem better or worse than 10 years ago? 20 years ago? 50 years ago? How is it projected to change in the future? This qualitative discussion is potentially aa good place to start engagement because it opens up social, cultural, historical avenues of exploration where communities get resilience and the interconnections with the natural environment."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How would you characterize the condition of your ecosystems (e.g., forests, agriculture, lakes, streams, coral reefs)?"/>
			<question text="What protective measures are in place for this ecosystem condition?"/>
			<question text="Are there changing climate, development, and/or environmental conditions that are presenting unique challenges to the ecosystem's health and wellbeing?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="21"
		system="Natural Environment"
		indicator="Species Health and Wellbeing"
		definition="The health and wellbeing of particular species."
		resilienceValue="Individual species play important roles in ecosystems and can have significant economic, physical, or  cultural value."
		equityValue="The health and wellbeing of species can vary dramatically across neighborhoods and racial, economic, and ethnic lines, based on access to resources and environmental protective measures."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="https://www.epa.gov/report-environment/diversity-and-biological-balance#roe-indicators"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess="This process depends on the place and the ecosystem, and so could be done many different ways. One way to get started is to browse the EPA ROE national indicators (https://www.epa.gov/report-environment/diversity-and-biological-balance#roe-indicators ) for locally relevant data. Next, search for local and state data sources on these topics."
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high species health for one or more species. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (habitat locally, regionally, across state boundaries, nationally, globally). 2. Consult with local parks and recreation, ecologists, and research personnel to determine past, current, and future characteristics of species health and how that may have (and will continue to) changed due to climate change. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="The species  may directly and indirectly supports human and societal needs, including providing food and nutrition, economic opportunity, recreation, physical health, emotional health, mental health, medicines, fresh water, and more. Consider past and future conditions - is the ecosystem better or worse than 10 years ago? 20 years ago? 50 years ago? How is it projected to change in the future? This qualitative discussion is potentially a good place to start engagement because it opens up social, cultural, historical avenues of exploration where communities get resilience and the interconnections with the natural environment."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="Are your most sensitive species populations stable, increasing or decreasing?"/>
			<question text="Are there any protection measures in place for these species?"/>
			<question text="Are there changing climate, development, and/or environmental conditions that are presenting unique challenges to the species' health and wellbeing?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>	
	<card
		id="22"
		system="Natural Environment"
		indicator="Land Cover and Habitat Connectivity"
		definition="Extent of continuous land connectivity for critical ecosystems, habitats, and species that support biodiversity taking into account fragmentation of landscapes by impervious surfaces and other urban development."
		resilienceValue="Intact and connected habitat can absorb rainwater and support species as they migrate or move to find food and suitable environmental conditions as the environmental conditions change."
		equityValue="Land cover type and extent of habitat connectivity can vary dramatically across neighborhoods and racial, economic, and ethnic lines, based on access to resources and environmental protective measures."
		localConcern="Our community is experiencing X, Y, Z, and sees the impacts on A, B, C"
		quantitativeDataSources="EPA Ecological Connectivity indicator: https://cfpub.epa.gov/roe/indicator.cfm?i=80 EPA EnviroAtlas: https://enviroatlas.epa.gov/enviroatlas/interactivemap/ Multi-Resolution Land Characteristics (MRLC) National Land Cover Database (NLCD): NLCD Land Cover Change Index https://www.mrlc.gov/data?f%5B0%5D=category%3ALand%20Cover&#38;f%5B1%5D=year%3A2019"
		quantitativeDataCollProcess=""
		qualitativeDataCollProcess="1. Host listening sessions with community members to determine low, medium, or high amounts of impervious surface and habitat connectivity. Make sure you identify the scale at which you are referencing (habitat locally, regionally, across state boundaries, nationally, globally). 2. Consult with local parks and recreation, ecologists, and research personnel to determine past, current, and future characteristics of species health and how that may have (and will continue to) changed due to climate change. 3. Cross check that information with community experience."
		additionalInformation="It may not make sense to connect land cover and habitat connectivity. Habitat connectivity may be a complex term that isn't directly relevant to community members."
		rawDataCollectionNotes=""
		dataPoints=""
		thresholds=""
	>
		<questionsToAnswer>
			<question text="How much of the community (or individual neighborhood) land cover is impervious?"/>
			<question text="What key habitat features remain intact and connected?"/>
			<question text="Have critical wildlife corridors and/or migratory pathways remained open and accessible for species movement and migration?"/>
		</questionsToAnswer>
	</card>		
</indicatorCards>